[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "What does \"Finally Free\" mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "``", "RB", "NNP", "''", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "The title speaks for itself.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "When you finished the book and you covered this extraordinary story, and we'll come to some of the details, what did you learn about Michael Vick?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "Well, I learned that I wasn't as forth right as I always wanted to be and thought I could be.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Vick"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "What was the lowest moment for you, of the whole thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "I think the lowest moment was when I, you know, I had to tell my son that I was going to prison and that I was going to be going for two years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "How do you deal with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "He just broke down crying.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "How did you -- how did you explain it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Well, the situation came about when his mom told me he had been getting teased by some of his friends at school, which is solely my fault, which is a situation that was out of my control.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "What you saw as an 8-year-old boy, although horrific, seemed exciting to you, did it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "Yes, because, you know, I always had a passion for animals and I always had a dog.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "And they'll say, how can you be a dog lover when you killed a lot of dogs because they were too weak to fight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "How can you be a dog lover that enjoys doing that, too?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "I know it may seem contradictory but, you know, that's just the person that I was.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "No parent, no family, no friend?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Nobody.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "When you were doing it, did you enjoy it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "You know, I enjoyed the competition aspect of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$130 million"]}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "$", "CD", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "And for what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "Just before the wall came crashing down on your life, you were the $130 million superstar.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "Did it make you somebody that now you don't really recognize?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "Yes, it did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "What did you think the moment you heard this has happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "I was on the golf course.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "Did you lie to them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "I lied to my mom.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "What was the moment you told your mother the truth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "I told her the truth the day I got -- I got arraigned.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "How did she react?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "She was just upset, disappointed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "I mean those first few weeks?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "Harder.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "What do you say to those who say the crime you did was just so awful, you shouldn't be even allowed to play football anymore?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "You know, I overlook it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "Do you blame them or do you understand it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "I understand it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "VB", "RB", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RBR", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "What was that moment like for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "You know, I was elated, you know, to get back home to my family, you know, more than anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Did you vow to yourself, you know, I'm never going to put my kids in this sort of position again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "Oh, yeah, before I even got home.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "What do you feel you owe her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "Everything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "Is it true the security alone for your wedding costs 300,000 dollars?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "That's false.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "Huh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "That's false.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "What were you doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "No, that's absurd.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 415, "question": "The fact that you're not just perceived as a footballer, you're a notorious celebrity?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 416, "answer": "You know, I'm so appreciative of my fans.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Or is it more important to you to be understood better?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "I think it's more important to be understood.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "Have you got a dog?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "You going to get one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "Maybe so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "Do you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "I mean, I would let them pick it out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "Or was it honestly more fun being the ne'er-do-well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "It was all kind of crazy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "How the devil are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "Do you know, I'm very, very happy today.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "I look different in that clip, huh?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "You do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["weekend"]}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", ":", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "How do you feel now that you're officially a single man again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "Well, I think that the -- what happened in the weekend was just an administrative finality.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "How is your life in reality at the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "Well, the limited amount of time I spend in reality I quite enjoy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "Have you become, you know, a little less excited about the whole nature of fame and celebrity?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Yes, I remember that interview very distinctly, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "Is there something society should do to try and put a lid on this before we all go completely mad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "What's the point of it all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "There isn't one, I don't think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "Are you an American resident yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "Is America refusing to accept you as one of its own then, Russell?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "I love the American people, all of them, every single individual.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Russell"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120717pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "How is your temper at the moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "Pretty good, mostly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]